<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<OnlineHelpDefinitions xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="\\spvaimapcn\data$\Apps\NoPAUSE\TPAS_XML_Library\XML Schemas\OnlineHelpDefinitions.xsd" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
  <Definitions>
    <Definition DefinitionId="Source dose" Text="Select the source dose distribution to convert from. If there are multiple relevant prior courses, convert each to EQD and create a sum in Eclipse before generating a BASE distribution"/>
    <Definition DefinitionId="Convert to" Text="Select the output distribution:&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>EQD2&lt;/b> and &lt;b>BED&lt;/b> are as traditionally defined, for a source physical dose distribution at its planned fractionation.&lt;br>&lt;br>&lt;b>EQDn#&lt;/b> is a BED-preserving transform between doses at different fractionations. For a source physical dose distribution at a given fractionation, EQDn# is the BED-equivalent physical source dose distribution in n (user-specified) fractions.&lt;br>&lt;br>The &lt;b>BASE&lt;/b> option outputs a dose distribution that, when used as a base dose for optimizing a new plan in n2 fractions, will result in the Max EQD2 constraint for each included structure (defined in the table) being exceeded in the sum only if the &lt;u>optimization&lt;/u> exceeds that EQD2 in the fractionation of the new plan (shown in the table as &lt;i>Eqv. in n#&lt;/i>). The input for BASE &lt;u>must be a EQD2 distribution&lt;/u>. The fractionation of the source distribution is ignored.&lt;br>&lt;br>For a source voxel with EQD2 dose d, and output in n#:&lt;br>&lt;br>BASE(d) = EQDn#(MaxEQD2) - EQDn#(MaxEQD2 - d)&lt;br>&lt;br>Note that the output dose will be zero in any region not covered by an included contour."/>
    <Definition DefinitionId="Max Equivalent Dose" Text="This is the physical dose, in the number of fractions above, that is equivalent to the Max EQD2 for the structure.&lt;br>&lt;br>When the BASE conversion is used as a base dose for a re-plan (in the number of fractions above), the sum of the source distribution and the EQD2 of the replan will not exceed the Max EQD2 if the optimization does not exceed this dose for the structure.&lt;br>&lt;br>Note that due to edge-effects, adding a small margin to the structure prior to conversion will make the process more reliable, particularly if the BASE dose just outside the structure is zero."/>
  <Definition DefinitionId="Include structure edges" Text="This option converts the dose voxels immediately surrounding the edge of the structure using the a/b ratio specified. For serial OARs where the limiting re-tx dose is likely to be at the periphery, this is a conservative approach."/>
  </Definitions>
</OnlineHelpDefinitions>
